vo5haircare.com 2016-07-16

# Privacy | VO5 Haircare

**ALBERTO VO5 WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY**

**General**

Welcome to the websites located at www.vo5haircare.com, operated by High Ridge Brands Co. (as used in this Privacy Policy, “we,” “us,” or “our”) (collectively, the “Website”). This Privacy Policy is effective as of, and was last updated on, 3/1/12.

The Website is intended for use only by persons at least 18 years of age residing in the United States, its territories and possessions. The Website is not intended for use by persons under the age of 13 under any circumstances, and if you are under 13 you should not use the Website. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Use, which govern your use of the Website. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use, you should not use the Website.

**Our Commitment to Your Privacy**

Thank you for visiting the Website. This Privacy Policy describes:

• how and why we collect certain information from you via the Website and the online services provided through the Website;

• how we use and with whom we share such information;

• how you can access and update such information; and

• the choices you can make about how we collect, use and share your information.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection and use practices, please contact us using the information in the Contact Us section below.

**Information We Collect**

We may request and/or collect personal information that you elect to provide to us (“Personal Information”) when you contact us with comments or feedback through the website. Personal Information we collect may include:

• contact information (e.g., name, email address and physical address);

• birth date; and

• your comments and feedback about the website.

When you submit our contact form containing this information, you have the opportunity to choose to receive promotional and/or other marketing information about products, services and offerings from us. We do not participate in bulk email solicitations that you have not consented to receiving (i.e., “spam”), and we will email you for marketing purposes only when you have indicated that you wish to receive marketing emails from us. Please refer to the “How to Update or Delete Your Personal Information” section below to learn how to revise the Personal Information we associate with you.

**Cookies**

We may use cookies to obtain non-personally identifiable information from Web site visitors. Such information may include your “Internet Protocol Address,” operating system, browser type and the referring Web site’s address, if any (“Non-Personal Information”). Cookies are files your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website. Depending on your browser, you may be able to reject cookies or indicate when a cookie has been sent. Cookies enable us to customize your user interface, to speed up your interactions with the Website, to improve the Website and to facilitate your navigation through the Website. We may use session cookies (which survive only as long as your browser is open) to perform these tasks. We may also use cookies in order to analyze your Non-Personal Information in order to improve our Website through our analytics provider, as indicated in the “Use and Disclosure” section below.

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

We use Personal Information to respond to your requests and answer your inquiries, to send you the marketing email you have requested, and for our internal operations purposes. In some cases, we may use a third party service provider to deliver our marketing emails, but they may only use the information we give them for the purpose of sending you the email you’ve requested.

The Personal Information that you provide will be available to us, our agents, representatives. In the future, we may disclose your Personal Information to trusted service providers and contractors for the limited purposes of providing services or information to you or analyzing and improving the Website. These categories of use include, but may not be limited to, communicating to Website visitors, offering certain products and services in connection with the Website (for example, we may ask for Personal Information in order to send you information, with your consent, on new products, special offers, and performance of the Company).

We may also use your Personal and Non-Personal information for the purposes of our internal analyses of our business and the Website. In some cases we may also use analytics software on the Website in order to better understand our customer demographics and our Website’s performance. When we do, that software accesses the Non-Personal Information gathered on the Website and that Non-Personal information may be associated with the Personal Information you have provided to us. The analytics provider is not permitted to use your Personal Information for any purpose other than the provision of analytics to us. We will also disclose Personal Information if in our opinion such disclosure is required (i) by law, (ii) to protect and/or defend our rights and/or (iii) to protect the personal safety of any individual. In addition, in the event that we engage in a business transition with another entity, we may transfer Personal Information to the acquiring or partner entity. We may disclose or use your Personal Information if we deem it necessary, in our sole discretion, to enforce our rights or to protect the safety and security of the Website or any other users.

**Storing and Securing Your Information**

Because none of the information you send to us is sensitive, we do not currently encrypt transmission to and from the Website. While we take reasonable efforts to ensure the security of information you send to us in our possession, please be aware that no transmission over the Internet can be completely secure. You assume the risk of sending any information to us, our affiliates, our partners, or other third parties over the Internet.

**Links**

There may be links from the Website to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to the Website and not to websites of any other company or organization linked to the Website. Accessing those third party websites or sources requires you to leave the Website, and your use of such third party websites is subject to those sites’ privacy policies and/or terms of service. We do not control those third party websites or any of the content contained therein and you expressly acknowledge and agree that we are in no way responsible or liable for any of those third party websites, including, without limitation, their content, policies, failures, promotions, products, services on or actions of those websites and/or any damages, losses, failures or problems caused by, related to or arising from those websites. We strongly encourage you to review all policies, rules, terms and regulations, including the privacy policies, of each website that you visit.

**Changes**

The Website policies, content, information, promotions, disclosures, disclaimers and features may be revised, modified, updated, and/or supplemented at any time and without prior notice in our sole and absolute discretion. Changes to this Privacy Policy may be made periodically as we update our Website, and you are responsible for reviewing this policy periodically in order to ensure that you are comfortable with our data handling practices when using the Website.

**How to Update or Delete Your Personal Information**

If you want us to remove your Personal Information from our database, you merely need to contact us by: (a) visiting us at www.VO5haircare and filling out an email to us or by emailing Info@highridgebrands.com requesting removal of or updates to your Personal Information or (b) by calling us at (800) 337-0787 and asking for Customer Relations.

If you ask us to delete any Personal Information we have about you, we will take all reasonable efforts to delete your Personal Information from our database within a reasonable time frame, but please be advised that we may retain some residual information about you in our backup and archival copies of our database (e.g. our records of deletion). We may use these backups to send you important service-related communications (e.g. materials related to your registration, your purchases and/or your account) that are not promotional in nature.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

A business subject to California Civil Code section 1798.83 is required to disclose to its California customers, upon request, the identity of any third parties to whom the business has disclosed personal information within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. This Policy explains each way in which we might disclose your information to third parties, but no such disclosure are for third parties’ marketing use. If you still have questions, please use the mechanism described in the “Contact Us” section below.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy and/or practices as it relates to any or all of the Website, please contact us at the following e-mail address and telephone number.

**Email**

Simply fill out the contact us information found at www.VO5haircare.com; once you finish typing in the information, click on submit and an email will be sent to us.

**Address**

ATTN: Privacy  
High Ridge Brands Co.  
5 High Ridge Park  
Suite 100  
Stamford, CT 06905

On occasion, mergers, acquisitions, and sales of business assets occur. In the event that Company ever is involved in such a transaction, then personal information may be disclosed to the entity that acquires, is acquired by, or merges with Company’s or purchases any of its assets.
